marketingvici.com 2017-06-06

# Vici can ensure that personal data shared with us is protected from loss, misuse or illegal alterations. All users’ information is stored in an encrypted format.

Privacy Policy
Gathering and Using Personal Data
When the website is visiting , the user’s IP address is collected and used to diagnose and
resolve problems with the server.
Visitor’s IP address could also be used to gather broad demographic information. In that
case, Vici shares personal data with advertisers and partners, but does not share
personally identifying information.
The company also provides services by means of periodic newsletters where visitors have
the option to request not to receive further email notifications.
On the Career page, users who wish to apply for a job at the company are asked to
provide personal information and submit a copy of their resume.
Vici also informs users about special promotions or any other information that can be of
interest. Visitors who choose not to receive email updates can disable this option.
Vici cannot guarantee that all private communications with users and other personal
information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in Privacy Policy. In
cases of investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is
illegal, Vici is required to provide personal data to government or third parties under
certain circumstances.
Linked Sites
Vici cannot be held responsible for the information or the security of other sites linked to its
website.
Security
Vici can ensure that personal data shared with us is protected from loss, misuse or illegal
alterations. All users’ information is stored in an encrypted format.
